socialmediaweek.org 2012-12-09

# Privacy Policy » Social Media Week

At Crowdcentric Media LLC (“Crowdcentric” or “we”), the global organizer of Social Media Week, we appreciate your personal privacy. This Privacy Policy is intended to explain what data we collect from Users of the Site.  The terms Site, Service and Member that are used in this Privacy Policy are defined in the [Terms of Use](http://dev.socialmediaweek.org/terms-of-use/).  A “User” means either a Member or a non-Member who is simply visiting the Site (a “Visitor”).  Our Service is intended for Users over thirteen (13) years of age and we will not intentionally collect or maintain information about anyone under thirteen (13) years of age. This Privacy Policy may be revised or updated at any time and we encourage you to check back often to ensure that you are familiar with the most recent version and the terms of our Privacy Policy.

###### When do we collect your personal information?

You may provide personally identifiable information (“PII”) to us in the following ways:

\+ by registering as a Member  
\+ by subscribing to our newsletter  
\+ by sharing personal information when you post comments on our blog posts, such as your email address or Twitter handle  
\+ by contacting us through our [Get Involved](http://dev.socialmediaweek.org/get-involved) page, or by emailing us at one of our email addresses listed on the Site, like our [Contact](http://socialmediaweek.org/contact) page  
+by providing us information through third party service providers, for example, registration software such as Eventbrite or promotional partners such as Thrillist

In addition to PII, we may also collect non-personally identifiable information (“NPII”) from Users when they visit the site.

###### What personal information do we collect?

Depending on the portion of the Site and Service that you interact with, PII we collect may include your:

\+ full name  
\+ email address  
\+ mailing address  
\+ profile photo you submit  
\+ Username or login IDs for Twitter, Facebook or Linked-in  
\+ Company, job title, industry, gender 

NPII we collect when you visit the Site may include:

\+ your IP address  
\+ your approximate geographic location  
\+ the operating system you are using  
\+ the Internet browser you are using  
\+ the Web page you requested to visit

###### How is my personal information used?

Depending on the portion of the Service and Site that you have subscribed to or interacted with, we may use your information in a number of ways:

\+ If you choose to subscribe (opt-in) to our newsletter, we will send our periodic newsletter to the email address you provided us. Members can opt-out of our newsletter at any time by clicking the “Unsubscribe” link that is present on every email at the very bottom of the newsletter.  
\+ The email address that you use when contacting us through our [Get Involved](http://socialmediaweek.org/conferences/get-involved) page or one of our email addresses listed on the Site (such as on our [Contact](http://socialmediaweek.org/conferences/contact) page) will not be used for any reason except for responding to your inquiry.  
\+ If you comment on the Site, and your comment violates our [Terms of Use](http://socialmediaweek.org/terms-of-use/), we may use the contact information you provided in order to comment to notify you of the policy violation.  
\+ From time to time, we may organize contests and other promotions. If you share information with us directly or through one of our third party service providers, we may use the email address you provided in order to notify you of the results  
\+ We may use your NPII to monitor Site usage trends and improve the User experience  
\+ We may disclose your PII if required to do so by process of law, or if necessary in order to investigate fraud, a violation of our [Terms of Use](http://socialmediaweek.org/terms-of-use/) or in connection with any harm being caused to a third party or their rights

###### Who else has access to my personal information?

Our Site may contain links to Internet sites or third party applications or widgets operated by other companies that we don’t own or control. These links might have been added by us or by a User, such as in a submitted comment. Regardless of who added a given link, we’re not responsible for the privacy practices of websites or other services operated by third parties. Once you leave the Site via such a link or access a third party application or widget, you should check the applicable privacy policy of that third party to determine how they will handle any PII they collect from you.

Below are the privacy policies of some of our third party service providers:

Disqus <http://docs.disqus.com/help/30/>

Eventbrite <http://www.eventbrite.com/privacypolicy/>

Amiando <http://www.amiando.com/legal/privacy.html>

For the majority of our events, we use a registration system that does not require any personal registration data to be shared with a third party provider. However, from time to time, we or our partners use registration systems that do share your personal registration data with the system provider (such as Eventbrite).

We use the third party provider DISQUS in order to allow you to comment on our Site by using your pre-existing Twitter or Facebook accounts.  Despite certain DISQUS communications to the contrary, we do not get access to your email address nor do we have any access to or control over your personal data or private information when you use your Twitter or Facebook account to comment on the Site.

Below are the privacy policies of some of the other third parties who may indirectly provide services to us:

Google <http://www.google.com/intl/en/privacy/>

Facebook <http://www.facebook.com/policy.php>

Twitter <http://twitter.com/privacy>

Foursquare <https://foursquare.com/legal/privacy>

If you register to attend a particular event in a particular city, and if the law permits, we may share your PII with: (a) our local organizing partner for that particular city; and (b) the event host who organized that particular event; however, we will not grant permission for those parties to share it with anyone else.

###### What about cookies?

Cookies are small bits of information that we might place on your computer. We would use cookies to identify your Internet browser, store Users’ preferences, and determine whether you have installed sufficient enabling software needed to access certain parts of the Service. Data in cookies may be read to authenticate user sessions or provide features of the Service.

You can program your computer to warn you each time a cookie is being sent, block third party cookies or block all cookies. However, by blocking all cookies you may not have access to certain features of the Service.

###### How do I edit my personal information?

Click “Edit Profile” to edit your personal information.  While most of the information in your profile can be edited, many of the fields are required in order to complete the modification to your profile.  Also please note that you cannot change your username.

###### How do I delete my Membership account?

If you would like to delete your Membership account, please send us an email from the email address that is associated with your Membership account at [info@socialmediaweek.org](mailto:info@socialmediaweek.org).  Please let us know your username in that email, so that we may complete your request accurately.

You should be aware that it may not be technologically possible to remove each and every record of the information you have provided to us from our servers. The need to back-up our systems to protect information from inadvertent loss means that a copy of your PII may exist in a non-erasable form that may be difficult or impossible for us to locate.

In addition, we have the right to delete any account at any time if required to do so by process of law, or if necessary in order to investigate fraud, a violation of our [Terms of Use](http://socialmediaweek.org/terms-of-use/) or in connection with any harm being caused to a third party or their rights.

###### How secure is my personal information?

We use commercially reasonable administrative, technical, personnel and physical measures to safeguard PII against loss, theft and unauthorized use, disclosure or modification.  However, we cannot completely guarantee the security of PII. Although we make commercially reasonable efforts to protect your PII from loss, misuse, or alteration by third parties, you should be aware that there is always some risk involved in transmitting information over the Internet.

We don’t collect or retain your personal financial information (“PFI”), such as credit card data.  If in the future we offer services that require you to provide your PFI, your PFI will be collected by, provided to and processed by a third party payment processor – not us – and their treatment of your PFI will be covered by their privacy policy.
